Driving the Need for Product and Process Measurement
Hello, Mike Harry, and welcome to this segment on measurement power.
We’re going to be looking at the absolute power of how measurements
can create improvement. Measurements are needed
to guide our way through process improvement.
And to sustain that process improvement.
Without a doubt measurement is power. Just as knowledge is power.
Without measurements, it becomes very difficult
to fly our plane, so to speak, literally and figuratively.
You see, these measurements are absolutely essential.
How would we fly an airplane without them?
Can you imagine getting on board an airliner and the pilot has no instruments?
Because measurement is at the base of instrumentation.
And instrumentation tells us what's going on.
That simple. We gotta be able to know that.
Understand where we’re at. Where we’re going.
And how to improve. Measurements are essential for that.